[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[mouse clicking]
Jin Isoo is late today.
We had a drink yesterday.
Did you?
[exhales] He must've lost again.
EPISODE 11
- Oh.
- [Changun] Uh...
Detective Joo.
We got a report from Jin Isoo's house.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
You should go check it out.
[tires screeching]
This way, please.
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[Younghwan laughing] Huh?
My friend, Jin Isoo. [laughs]
[Isoo] Younghwan, you, again!
You want to try, too?
No! Please... Don't!
I told you I'd never see you
if you did it again.
You should undergo
a proper investigation and quit drugs.
All my life,
I've never thought of you as a friend.
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
Jin Isoo.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
That's Kim Younghwan.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
What happened?
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
[♪ music fades]
Do you two know who the victim is?
He's Isoo's friend from middle school.
He was the CEO
of the production company Isoo owns.
Isoo personally arrested him for drugs.
I looked into it,
and he was released two months ago.
What happened?
What time did you get home
after we split up?
I think it was after 10:00 p.m.
And then?
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
[sighs softly]
[digital lock beeps]
[Younghwan laughing]
Look who's here!
My friend, Jin Isoo!
I've been waiting for you.
What took you so long?
How did you...
[chuckles softly]
I gave you a key before.
[chuckles] Exactly.
To your best friend. Did you forget?
Wait a minute, you bastard.
Did you erase
my very existence from your memory?
Yes, I did.
So just leave.
Come on, don't be like that. It hurts.
Just come sit down.
Uh...
[sighs] You did a fine job making this.
It's classy.
Tasty, too. [chuckles]
What are you playing at?
Your friend came to visit, you asshole.
Let's have a drink like old times.
Drink up.
[sighs softly]
[exhales sharply]
Didn't you miss me?
Finish your drink and go.
As for me,
I thought about you a lot.
ONE WEEK EARLIER
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Hey.
Were you the one
who came in here last week?
[chuckling]
Bingo!
[laughs smugly]
I came because I missed you so much.
You didn't even visit me in prison,
or bother to come the day I got out.
If you were the one to put me away,
the least you could've done
was check in on me.
After all those years I spent
as your damn sidekick.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't get over it.
But what do you know?
[vocalizing victory fanfare]
[laughs smugly]
I have a key to your house.
[breathes deeply]
You knocked yourself out
with sleeping pills
and couldn't remember a damn thing.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ ominous music playing]
MR. JIN ISOO
You're nothing, you piece of shit.
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[blunt thud]
[clattering]
- [exclaims]
- [glass shattering]
[exclaims]
[breathing heavily]
[shatters]
[laughing maniacally]
[♪ music swells]
[exclaims, continues laughing]
I could have killed you.
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
I sent you to prison
to straighten you out,
but you came back worse.
Hey,
get up and leave while I'm being nice.
What about you?
What would happen
if the great Jin Isoo ended up in prison?
[scoffs] Now that would be
quite a sight, right?
Cut the crap and get up.
Do I have to drag you out?
[scoffs softly]
Okay, fine.
[in English] Okay. [grunts]
My key.
[in Korean] Right, your key.
[scoffs]
[key card slaps on table]
That hurts, you asshole.
[sighs in exasperation]
Let's shake hands one last time.
I'm moving abroad.
I can't live here
after the way you humiliated me.
[exhales softly]
[♪ music turns ominous]
[laughing maliciously]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Jin Isoo.
Enjoy the fall.
You're finished.
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[dull, distorted audio]
[high-pitched tone droning]
- [♪ music swells, fades]
- [muffled thuds]
- [audio normalizes]
- [Younghwan laughing maliciously, echoes]
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
[chair squeaks]
[sighs in despair]
That's all?
I don't remember anything after that.
I think I passed out.
[Kyungjin] How can you not remember?
You're... [sighs softly]
This is driving me crazy, too.
How on earth did this happen?
[door bursts open]
[Taegyun] What the hell is going on?
[♪ music fades]
[exhales deeply]
Joo Hyera. I told you, didn't I?
I said he was going to cause trouble!
[exclaims incredulously]
You kept defending him.
A police detective killed someone.
How are you going to fix this?
- We still need to investigate.
- Investigate what?
Jin Isoo and the victim were
the only ones inside the house!
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
Hand over the case
to the Metropolitan Detective Unit.
And you, come with me!
[Taegyun scoffs softly]
- [door slams]
- [sighs softly]
[Kyungjin sighs heavily]
Jin Isoo.
You need to get it together
and remember anything you can.
[sighs grimly]
Where is Jin Isoo?
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
What are you going to do?
We're arresting him without a warrant.
He has money and power.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE
KANG MUJIN
No one's a bigger flight risk.
Go and bring him out.
- [detective 1] Yes, sir.
- [detective 2] Yes, sir.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[detective 1] Come with us.
[Isoo grunts softly]
[sighs softly]
[Mujin] Mr. Jin Isoo,
you are under arrest
for the murder of Kim Younghwan.
You have the right to an attorney
and the right to remain silent.
You won't be penalized
for remaining silent.
You'll have a chance to explain yourself.
[♪ music swells]
I'm sure you know from playing detective.
Let's go.
Please go out the back.
There are reporters outside.
[♪ music fades]
It really does pay to be a chaebol.
How much will I get for that favor?
Maybe 100 million won?
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
He's not the killer.
He would never kill anyone.
[sighs softly]
How much has he been slipping you
to make you say crap like that?
You should worry about yourselves.
Internal Affairs will be here soon.
Let's go.
[door opens]
[scoffs softly]
[door closes]
[camera shutters clicking]
[reporter 1] Is it true
that you murdered someone?
[reporter 2] Is it true
that the victim was a friend?
- [reporter 3] Why did you kill him?
- [reporter 4] Mr. Jin Isoo!
Do you admit to the murder?
- [reporter 5] Was the murder premeditated?
- [reporter 6] Do you admit to it?
[reporters clamoring]
[♪ tense, somber music playing]
[clamoring continues]
- [reporter 6] Mr. Jin Isoo!
- [siren blaring]
[reporter 7] Mr. Jin Isoo!
[clamor subsides]
What do we do?
[♪ music fades]
[♪ pulsating ominous music playing]
- [cell phone vibrating]
- [♪ music fades]
JUNYOUNG
- [line ringing, connects]
- [Dr. Yoon] Junyoung.
Did you see the body?
[Dr. Yoon] Yes,
I'm looking at him right now.
He was stabbed without hesitation.
Did Detective Jin really do this?
Absolutely not.
It wasn't Isoo.
[sighs softly]
[♪ suspenseful, ticking music playing]
[Mujin] How do you know Kim Younghwan?
You're old friends
and started a production company together?
Yes.
But you arrested him for doing drugs.
[sighs wearily]
He couldn't get off drugs,
so I turned him over to Narcotics.
You're a good friend.
But Kim Younghwan must've been mad.
His friend had betrayed him.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Kim Younghwan entered your home
at 9:00 p.m. and waited for you.
[card reader beeps]
You had a fight, didn't you?
Things weren't exactly
pleasant between us.
I told him to just leave.
If you had a fight,
why did you do drugs together?
[♪ music fades]
Drugs?
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[Mujin] This is the drug test
you just took.
Judging by the levels,
you were completely out of it yesterday.
NARCOTICS DETECTED
I don't do drugs.
Then how do you explain this?
[sighs in despair]
Jin Isoo.
Enjoy the fall.
You're finished.
[dull, distorted audio]
[muffled thuds]
A drug that can be absorbed
through skin contact.
I think that's what got me.
I don't remember anything
after shaking hands with Younghwan.
[scoffs]
Are you claiming diminished capacity?
It's the truth.
My team found a drug called "Ruby"
during one of our investigations.
I think it was a similar drug.
[sighs heavily]
[♪ music fades]
We're both detectives here,
so let's be honest.
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
Imagine you're the detective in charge.
Only the victim and the suspect
were present on site.
The two of them are friends,
but the suspect got the victim
convicted on drug charges.
It's enough for a grudge.
The victim was mad
and entered the suspect's home.
The victim died,
and the suspect was high on drugs.
That's not all.
The suspect is a chaebol
who does whatever he wants,
and he carries the trauma
of having both his parents murdered.
What do you think?
He looks guilty to you too, right?
It really wasn't me.
Then why did Kim Younghwan die?
Did he kill himself?
You said someone reported it.
Are you investigating them?
[scoffs]
I am.
Who is it?
You can listen to it yourself.
[Isoo, over recording]
Hello? Please get the police here.
I killed someone.
[dispatcher] Sir, what is your name?
[Isoo] Jin Isoo.
I'm at my house.
[scoffs]
What?
Got nothing left to argue?
[♪ music increases in tempo]
- [Mr. Choi exhales sharply]
- [Mujin sighs]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
I'm done here, so feel free to talk.
[door closes]
[Mr. Choi sighs softly]
[♪ music fades]
[Changun] Don't get involved
and just stay put.
And make sure Park and Choi
don't do anything stupid.
Internal Affairs will be here.
If anything goes wrong,
all your careers are over.
- Leave it with the Metropolitan Unit.
- I can't.
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
They already have a story worked out.
They won't consider
any other possibilities.
Jin Isoo killing someone?
I don't believe it.
You never know with people.
Jin Isoo could be the killer.
Even if that's true,
I need to see it for myself.
Hey, Joo Hyera.
Sir.
If I were in this situation,
would you stand by and do nothing?
[sighs wearily]
For now, there is a way
to prevent him from being detained.
We can dispute this warrantless arrest.
[Isoo] Please don't do that.
I'm a police detective.
I can't use a legal loophole
to run away from this.
Isoo.
This isn't the time for that.
[Isoo] Mr. Choi.
I didn't do it.
I need to catch...
whoever did this.
[Mr. Choi sighs heavily]
[♪ music fades]
Detective Jin Isoo of Gangha Police,
known for being a chaebol heir,
has been arrested on a murder charge.
Police reportedly made
a warrantless arrest
after the victim's body was found
inside his home.
With public attention focused on this case
involving the family
that owns Hansu Group,
police are investigating the circumstances
surrounding the incident.
[news anchor] Detective Jin Isoo,
the chaebol heir
currently working as a detective,
was arrested on suspicion of murder.
What exactly transpired?
[reporter] Yes, a body was found
inside the home of Detective Jin Isoo.
Detective Jin Isoo was
the only person inside the house,
and an arrest warrant was issued after
multiple pieces of evidence were found.
He is currently being questioned
by Seoul Metropolitan Police.
Isoo's gotten himself into trouble.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
[Younghwan, laughing] Look who's here!
My friend, Jin Isoo!
As for me, I thought about you a lot.
What would happen
if the great Jin Isoo ended up in prison?
Let's shake hands one last time.
[laughing maliciously]
- [heavy thud]
- Jin Isoo.
Enjoy the fall.
[♪ music fades]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
[door closes]
Detective Joo, what do we do?
[Junyoung] Let's investigate it ourselves.
There's no way Isoo did this.
[Kyungjin] We need to do something.
There's too much evidence against him.
If this goes to trial now, he's finished.
[breathes deeply]
Getting worked up won't help.
You two should stay put.
Are you going to do this alone?
[sighs softly]
What are you all whispering about?
- [door closes]
- You three look way too suspicious.
Are you going to investigate
Jin Isoo's case?
Hey,
if you three make a move, don't you think
that will draw attention, huh?
We'll look into it quietly.
[♪ quirky music playing]
[Junyoung] What?
Hey, Jin Isoo may be a pain,
but at the end of the day,
he's one of our own.
Then, please get us the forensics report,
the vehicle log at the time of the crime,
and the building's security footage.
Oh, you always have a plan, Detective Joo.
Okay, got it.
Will you be able to manage all of that?
What do you take me for, you punk?
Do you know how many
connections I have in this field?
In the world of police,
I'm basically an influencer.
[♪ music fades]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
We're from Internal Affairs.
Senior Inspector Joo Hyera,
Inspector Park Junyoung,
Senior Police Officer Choi Kyungjin.
Come with us.
[♪ music swells, fades]
Did you know
Detective Jin Isoo is a drug addict?
No.
Drugs were found in his system.
A fairly large amount.
How could you work with him and not know?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Kyungjin] Drugs?
No. He'd never do such a thing.
Someone must've drugged him.
This was a setup!
Anger-management issues?
He arrested his half-brother,
who killed his parents.
If it were me, I would've killed him.
Then did you know
he was seeing a psychiatrist?
No, I didn't know.
After his mother was murdered, he was
receiving treatment for a very long time.
You didn't know that either?
I didn't know.
Besides, that fact
has nothing to do with this case.
Why wouldn't it?
I'm saying Jin Isoo is mentally ill.
Please watch what you say.
[inhales sharply] Maybe you knowingly
cleaned things up for him.
He paid you, didn't he?
[scoffs softly]
No, he didn't.
We'll be looking into your bank accounts,
so bear that in mind.
[♪ gentle, somber music playing]
What I really want to know
is why Senior Inspector Joo Hyera,
an elite officer who climbed
the ranks in record time,
went to Gangha Police Station
to play gofer for a chaebol.
[inhales sharply] Did he promise you
a cushy job down the line?
Jin Isoo
is a capable and responsible detective.
Someone who's narrow-minded
won't be able to see that.
[♪ music fades]
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR SEO JOOHEE
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR KIM JINSEO
CHAIRMAN CHOI JEONGHUN
PRESIDENT JIN MYUNGJAE
BOARD CHAIR KUK MINGYUN
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
As you all know,
Detective Jin Isoo was arrested
on a murder charge,
so we have called
an emergency board meeting.
Did he actually kill someone?
It's still under investigation,
but I don't believe he did.
I'm not asking what you think, Chairman.
Guilty or not, our company's reputation
is going to take a nosedive!
The public is saying we're a company of
murderers owned by a family of murderers.
Why did he have to go out there
to play detective, huh?
He already caused trouble
with that bombing incident.
You've known him since he was a child.
Didn't you see this coming?
The Jin Isoo I know
would never do something like this.
Until the investigation is concluded,
I ask for your patience.
How can you say that
when they have all the evidence?
That's not all.
Detective Jin Isoo used
Hansu Air Space's high-altitude UAV
for personal purposes.
[all murmuring]
Did you know about this?
Yes.
I authorized it.
What?
[murmuring continues]
[Mr. Choi] I apologize.
What on earth...
The press will be all over this.
What are you going to do?
It would seem
we need someone to take responsibility.
[♪ music swells]
Please step down.
[♪ music fades]
I heard you're not even
in the best of health.
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
- [Mr. Choi clears throat]
- [♪ music fades]
- [Mingyun] Great job today.
- [IA investigator] You too.
DETECTIVE DIVISION
What's going to happen to Detective Jin?
What do you think?
The case will go to prosecutors on Monday.
What?
You mean you already
concluded the investigation?
The drugs, the weapon, the fingerprints.
There's more than enough evidence.
If Jin Isoo isn't the real culprit,
if he was set up,
how will you answer for this?
I'll answer for it, in my own way.
So you three
should also answer
for all the crimes you've committed.
[♪ tense music playing]
Let's go.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[keys jingling]
[♪ music fades]
[lock clicks open]
[gate latch clanks]
Mr. Jin Isoo, you have a visitor.
Isoo!
What are you doing here?
I was worried about you.
What on earth happened?
Did you really
kill Younghwan?
No, I didn't.
Are you sure you didn't?
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
I had a feeling
this day would come.
From the first day I met you.
And about Seungju.
I couldn't understand
why you didn't kill him.
He murdered your parents.
You probably had
plenty of opportunities to kill him.
What are you talking about?
I'm not like you.
Are you sure?
Weren't you holding back all this time?
Then you took it all out on Younghwan.
Think back carefully.
Remember how good it felt
when you stabbed Younghwan.
That's who you are.
Stop talking nonsense and go.
[thud]
Don't run away from this.
Once you accept it,
you'll finally be free.
After all, you're my Little Prince.
[♪ music fades]
[Byungsik] This guy, Kim Younghwan.
He didn't do much
after he was released from prison.
And the security footage?
Here you go.
And this is the forensics report.
CRIME SCENE FORENSICS REPORT
And here's the list of vehicles.
You got these really quickly. Thank you.
We should get Jin Isoo out of there.
He grew up pampered.
I bet he's crying right about now.
[chuckles softly]
[gate latch clanks]
[inmate exhales, sniffles]
[groans softly]
[gate clicks]
[gate latch clanks]
- [keys jingle]
- [lock clicks]
Excuse me, sir. Sir!
Can I get something to eat?
I'm starving to death!
You're so mean.
[sniffles sharply]
[exhales softly]
Jin Isoo.
Flex Cop.
[♪ quirky, suspenseful music playing]
Ah, yes.
Wow. It's great to meet you. I follow you.
Can I get a photo with you?
[laughs heartily]
I don't have my phone.
Sir! Can I borrow your phone?
- To take a picture.
- [guard] Be quiet.
You're so mean.
Bro, then I suppose we could at least...
Let's hug.
[muffled] One second. [sniffles softly]
[gags, retching]
[exhales heavily]
[slurping]
[♪ music fades]
You can still eat
after throwing up like that?
[exhales contentedly] The drugs wore off.
Are you in here for doing drugs?
I can't really remember.
I was having a great time in a club,
and I felt a bit hot,
then they found me on a swing, butt naked.
[chuckling]
By any chance,
do you know a drug
that can be absorbed through the skin?
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
There's Ruby.
There's also "Touch."
Just by holding it like this,
it gives you an instant kick.
But it's super potent.
That stuff is nasty.
But I don't do that kind of stuff.
If you use that drug for the first time,
can it make you violent?
That's usually what happens.
How should I put this?
People with all those pent-up emotions,
with a lot of negative feelings
end up causing trouble.
The truth is,
when I first did it,
I broke all these windows
and caused a huge scene.
But, bro,
did you do drugs and do something bad?
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[Younghwan] Jin Isoo. Enjoy the fall.
[Younghwan laughing maniacally]
[audio distorts]
[♪ music swells]
[high-pitched tone droning]
[♪ eerie, suspenseful music playing]
[squelch]
[muffled metallic clinking]
[metallic clinking intensifies]
[inmate] What's wrong? Come on, breathe!
[audio normalizes]
Breathe!
[Isoo breathing heavily]
Are you okay?
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
FORENSIC CHEMISTRY REPORT
[Isoo, over recording] Hello?
Please get the police here.
I killed someone.
Jin Isoo.
[mouse clicks]
Hello? Please get the police here.
I killed...
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
FORENSIC REPORT
NAME: KIM YOUNGHWAN
[Hyera] The initial stabbing is believed
to have been near the foot of the stairs.
A 5 cm stab wound to the left chest,
2 cm and 4 cm stab wounds
to the left abdomen,
along with defensive wounds
to the left palm.
Defensive wounds on the chest,
abdomen, and hand were found.
- [Younghwan grunts]
- [squelching]
[groans]
[Hyera] The marks suggest
the victim crawled unaided.
[grunts]
- [squelch]
- [Younghwan exclaims]
[Hyera] A 3 cm stab wound
was found on the back.
The victim is believed to have died from
blood loss caused by multiple stab wounds.
Approximately 2.4 m from the resting point
near the stairs to the sofa,
smear marks believed to be
evidence of dragging were found.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[killer grunts]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[♪ music fades]
[sighs softly]
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[doorbell chiming]
[knocking at door]
[Hyera, over monitor]
I'm with the police. Is anyone home?
- [softly] Oh!
- [♪ music resumes tempo]
Show me your ID.
PUBLIC OFFICIAL ID
JOO HYERA
- Are you really a police officer?
- [♪ music fades]
Yes, I really am.
Come in.
Are you a singer?
Oh... [chuckles]
Yes, that's right. I'm Ko Danbi.
Ah.
Do you know about the incident
that happened next door a few days ago?
I do.
I finally found this house,
but now I have to move again.
[sighs] I don't feel safe
living here anymore.
But why are you handling it like this?
- Sorry?
- I mean, Jin Isoo isn't the killer.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What are you talking about?
Someone else went into that house. A man.
How do you know that?
You know what happened
to me last year, right?
Uh... [chuckles]
I'm afraid I don't.
Oh...
I guess you don't read celebrity gossip.
There was this crazy stalker
who was obsessed with me last year.
He hid in the stairwell
every day and watched me,
then eventually broke into my house.
I came home after a performance
to find him lying on my bed.
I moved here because I heard
it was the safest place around,
but I couldn't sleep anymore.
After that, I became an alcoholic.
I'm on medication for anxiety,
and I haven't been able to perform.
[sighs heavily]
It's really easy to ruin someone's life.
But about you seeing someone...
Ah.
There's a sensor in front of my door.
My intercom monitor turns on
when someone walks by.
[monitor beeping]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
Around 30 minutes later...
[monitor beeping]
...some guy walked past.
[slurps]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
Your hair isn't looking so great.
I didn't wash it.
[chuckles softly] Are you at least eating?
I don't have an appetite.
You should still eat something.
Why do you look so down?
I'm just not used to this place yet.
Why get used to it?
You'll be coming out soon.
The Metropolitan Unit didn't
investigate properly.
In their eyes... [sighs]
...I probably look guilty.
The truth is,
I'm on psychiatric medication.
I know.
You have panic disorder.
If, by some chance,
I really did kill him...
[Hyera] Hey.
Snap out of it.
A few days in lockup
and you've gone all pathetic.
Well, I mean,
I'm not exactly
the most trustworthy person.
Why not?
I trust you.
We believe you're innocent,
and we're still investigating the case.
After you went home,
a man entered your house.
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
A man?
Your neighbor's camera caught him.
You were drugged, then he went inside
and killed Kim Younghwan.
[exhales incredulously]
Are you going to snap out of it?
Yeah.
You just think about
what the killer's after.
Who and why would someone do this?
They could've just killed you,
but put you in here instead.
Okay.
Ah.
Yu Seongwon came here.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
Yu Seongwon?
Why?
I don't know.
He told me to accept
that this is who I am.
He looked happy that I was a murderer.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Could this be
Yu Seongwon's doing?
Yu Seongwon?
Why would he?
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[mouse clicks]
[doorbell chiming]
Hyera.
Coffee?
[chuckles softly]
In the middle of the night?
What happened with Detective Jin?
[sighs heavily]
We're still looking into it.
I think he was set up.
[inhales sharply]
Just maybe,
could it have been Yu Seongwon?
- Yu Seongwon?
- Yes.
When he found our cameras,
what if he realized Isoo was on our side
and set the whole thing up?
But he hasn't moved
since breaking our cameras.
Really?
I heard he came to see Jin Isoo.
I followed him that time.
I put a tracker on his car.
[engine roaring]
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[♪ music swells]
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
YU SEONGWON
STUDIO
[♪ music fades]
What's that?
Ah...
After Detective Jin was arrested,
the high-altitude UAV got disconnected.
- I guess they found out.
- So?
Yours truly went in the middle
of the night to install it.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
VIEWCAM
- Why didn't you tell me?
- [♪ music fades]
I figured you'd be busy.
I can handle this much on my own.
[scoffs]
You're really on the ball now.
I'm a one-man operation.
[Minjae chuckles]
Anyway, what did Yu Seongwon say to him?
That he knew Jin Isoo would commit murder.
[♪ ominous music playing]
He found it amusing.
What do you mean?
That's why I thought
maybe Yu Seongwon was behind this.
But this isn't how he does things.
He kidnaps people and kills them.
What does Jin Isoo mean to Yu Seongwon?
That's what I don't get.
You're right.
I think Isoo does mean
something special to him.
[♪ music fades]
What are you going to do now?
We have a suspect,
so we'll have to catch him first.
Call me if you need anything.
[chuckles] Okay. Call me
if anything happens with Yu Seongwon.
Don't act alone again.
Okay, I got it.
[chuckles softly]
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE
DETECTIVE UNIT 1
[detectives chattering, laughing]
[sighs] What do you want this early?
Don't you have work to do?
We came to save you.
You haven't turned Jin Isoo over
to the prosecutors yet, right?
[scoffs]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
Thirty minutes after
Detective Jin went inside,
this man went toward his house.
He was caught on the neighbor's camera.
So what? What about this man?
He's a suspect.
I'm saying it's possible
that this man killed Kim Younghwan.
[scoffs]
Are you serious?
How will you prove
that this guy killed him?
We can if we catch him.
[sighs heavily]
Either way, it's true
that Jin Isoo did drugs.
This guy might've been called
to clean up after him.
[Junyoung] That drug
was applied to Detective Jin's hand
by the victim.
[♪ music fades]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music resumes]
It's a drug called "Touch."
It absorbs right away through the skin,
and Detective Jin was drugged that way.
[camera shutter clicks]
Traces of Touch was found
on the victim's hand.
[camera shutter clicking]
As for the call that came in,
I guess you're not
very familiar with this.
Please listen to it again, carefully.
[♪ music fades]
[Isoo, over recording] Hello?
Please get the police here.
I killed someone.
Jin Isoo.
I'm at my house.
I know. I heard it all.
[exclaims] You don't know.
When you record something,
even if it sounds silent,
it still captures "room tone,"
which is like the hum of a fridge.
But it's not there.
[♪ quirky, dramatic music playing]
In other words, it's fake.
Software's so good these days
that it only takes three minutes to make.
So what?
We've identified the suspect.
If the real killer is caught,
what will happen?
[Kyungjin, clears throat]
The press will have a field day.
That's going to be
really embarrassing for you.
Hansu Group won't just stand by.
They'll sue right away.
Their reputation took a nosedive.
[Kyungjin] That aside,
I'm worried about Isoo.
I bet he's really angry.
I'd lose it, too.
- That would give anyone anger issues.
- [Kyungjin sighs]
I told you I would save you.
I can't do anything about you
facing disciplinary action for negligence,
but I can stop Detective Jin
and Hansu Group from suing you.
[sighs in exasperation]
Please release Jin Isoo.
[♪ music fades]
What's taking so long?
I'm sure Detective Kang is busy
making excuses left and right.
Bro!
[♪ gentle, poignant music playing]
[exhales contentedly]
Did you get out after 10 years?
That's just how I feel.
One day felt like a decade.
[chuckles softly]
You made it through.
Here.
PUBLIC OFFICIAL ID
JIN ISOO
Let's go.
Where are we going?
[Kyungjin] To celebrate.
Celebrating your release.
Ah, not your release,
but for not getting charged.
[scoffs softly]
Let's go, bro.
Don't link arms like this.
- I've been traumatized. Let go.
- [♪ music fades]
Mmm. Mix in the truffle like this.
[exclaims] Mmm!
Hey, slow down.
I haven't eaten in three days.
Look at my hollow eyes.
Isn't it nice, being together like this
and enjoying good food, mmm?
Eat up.
- [sighs deeply]
- [Isoo] Mmm!
[Hyera] Here.
Eat more.
What's this?
Why are you being so nice?
Fine, then don't.
Detective Park, eat up.
Yes, thank you.
This truffle aroma is amazing.
Hey! Give it here. It's mine.
[Kyungjin, grunts]
There's so many people here.
It's become really popular now.
Where did you run off to?
Bro.
Ta-da!
What are you doing?
Just have one bite.
It's bad luck otherwise.
Hey, hey!
I'm already a lucky guy. Super lucky.
- No way.
- Just one bite.
- No!
- Open up. Ah...
- [Isoo] Seriously.
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
You have some, too. Just to be safe.
Eat it as a precaution.
Have more. There you go.
[♪ music fades]
[Hyera] We found the suspect. [sighs]
Cho Pilgu.
Do you know him?
No. How did you find him?
He's a professional. Four prior
convictions, assault and murder.
He's extremely methodical.
He left by subway, so we spent all night
checking footage from all the stations.
He's the one who killed Kim Younghwan.
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
[phone clinks]
We'll have to catch him first.
- Stakeout starts tomorrow.
- Got it.
- [in English] Okay. [in Korean] Cheers.
- [Isoo grunts]
- [clinking]
[♪ music fades]
Tomorrow?
All right.
[Isoo] Honk, honk.
Why do you look so serious?
[sighs in relief]
I heard you were released today.
You knew?
Then you should've come with some tofu.
I'm sorry.
I had something going on.
Thank you.
- [sighs softly]
- [Mr. Choi] Mmm.
What happened with the case?
We identified a suspect.
We need to catch the guy
who killed Younghwan.
What was it like in jail?
[sighs heavily] It was the worst.
People were throwing up
and snoring next to me.
Crime really doesn't pay.
Wait, I didn't even commit one.
You've been through a lot.
You're worried about me right now?
I heard they're voting you out.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
Ah... [sighs]
You heard?
What's the reason?
Well...
For various reasons.
It was my uncle, wasn't it?
Unbelievable.
He always tries to worm his way in.
No, you're wrong.
It's just time.
So what, you'll go travel the world?
You'll shake it all off
and forget all about me?
[chuckles softly]
I have to go. It's my dream.
[sighs softly]
[♪ music fades]
[Mingyun] We will now vote
on the motion to remove the CEO.
All those in favor, raise your hand.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[sighs softly]
With this, the motion to remove the CEO,
Mr. Choi Jeonghun, has passed.
Chairman Choi.
Thank you for all your hard work.
Everyone, let's get up and go.
[♪ music fades]
It's been a while since I came in,
and there was an important meeting.
Please, everyone, have a seat.
- Mr. Kuk.
- [Mingyun] Yes?
What motion was passed?
Uh, the motion to remove the CEO.
- Really?
- [Mingyun] Yes.
What was the reason?
He's not in the best of health.
The surgery went well,
and he's recovering just fine.
What else?
Uh, the unauthorized
high-altitude UAV use.
That was my request.
[♪ tense, ticking music playing]
Anything else?
Uh...
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
It seems after my arrest,
you were all used by someone
who wants to be the CEO.
How can I possibly trust this board?
This isn't your place to interfere.
As Hansu Group's largest shareholder
and non-executive director,
I propose a motion to reappoint
Mr. Choi Jeonghun as CEO.
- Let's vote right away.
- What are you doing?
[♪ music increases in tempo]
You think this is a joke?
All in favor,
raise your hand.
It looks like the matter has been settled.
You should all go. You must be busy.
They say you get less greedy with age.
You should really let go now.
Ah, then again, I do understand.
Your younger brother always outshone you.
No wonder you're bitter.
But you should know,
you're no match for me either, Uncle.
[♪ electric guitar chord swells]
[♪ music fades]
Why did you do that?
There's no one better suited
to be CEO of Hansu Group than you.
And I refuse to let you
be pushed out like this because of me.
[♪ gentle, poignant music playing]
My uncle's a mean person.
It'd be bad news
if someone like him became CEO.
[chuckles]
I'll personally send you
on that trip myself.
But until then,
please look after the company.
Oh no, I'm late. I'd better go.
- [sighs heavily]
- [♪ music fades]
[line ringing]
- Where is Jin Isoo?
- He won't answer his phone.
[automated voice]
The number you have dialed...
- [in English] I'm back.
- Bro.
What are you wearing?
[in Korean] I had to stop by somewhere.
- Are you a trot singer?
- Close enough.
Cho Pilgu is inside his house.
There on the second floor.
Detective Park and I will go up.
You stay out of sight.
Okay, fine. I'll hide near the entrance.
- Me too.
- [Isoo] Okay.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
Cho Pilgu is dangerous.
We have to be careful.
- Got it.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[doorbell chiming]
[Junyoung] I'm from the post office.
[Pilgu] What do you want?
Am I speaking to Mr. Cho Pilgu?
I have a court document
that has to be delivered to you in person.
[♪ music resumes tempo]
Could you sign right here?
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[Junyoung and Kyungjin grunting]
[Junyoung grunts, groans]
Cho Pilgu.
- [Pilgu grunts]
- [shattering]
[Pilgu grunts, exhales heavily]
- Hey, Cho Pilgu.
- [glass shard scrapes]
- [Pilgu grunts]
- [fabric rips]
You asshole. This is expensive.
[both panting]
- [Junyoung grunts]
- [Kyungjin swears softly]
[Hyera panting]
[cycle clatters]
- [grunts]
- [shattering]
[Isoo groans]
[panting]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[grunts, panting]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music continues]
[exhales, panting]
[continues panting] Oh, oh...
[Isoo continues panting]
Kid, go inside.
Go inside!
[exhales anxiously]
Your heart's pounding.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[kid breathing shakily]
Drop the knife.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 11
THE CHASE COMES TO A HEAD
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
Special Cast. Min Kyoungah
Why did you kill Younghwan?
[Kyungjin] Cho Pilgu collapsed!
[Isoo] But I can't see the bigger picture.
[Junyoung] Forensics didn't find anything.
You think you're perfect, don't you?
I'm working on a new piece.
Would you like to see?
Are you going to trust someone like her?
You shut your mouth.
You have no manners.
You should be careful.
I think we'll have to kill him.
Find someone.
I'm a lawyer.
[Seongwon] Make him cause an accident.
It's going to be so much fun.
Where's Detective Joo?
How did we get a body delivered?
[gasps, sobbing]
[♪ music fades]
[cell phone vibrating]
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
[cell phone continues vibrating]
[Pilgu] Mr. Lawyer.
I've been caught.
[sighs softly]
[whispering] You'd better hurry.
Translated by Hyesoo Lee